Visit turkision.com for more!
Osman Bey is coming!
Osman Bey is coming
Osman Bey is bringing the prisoners!
Welcome Osman Bey! Long live Osman Bey!
Welcome Osman Bey! Long live OsmarTBey!
May witches take your life!
May souls fall onto you like nightmares, Osman!
Welcome Osman Bey!
Peace be with you.
Peace be upon you.
Welcome, my Bey.
Come on then.
No.
Don't make the Beys kneel.
Oh people, my Beys, my Alps.
Mekece Castle...
...with the help of Allah...
...has become Kayi's property.
Thank Allah.
Long live Osman Bey!
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
Thank Allah, without any martyrs...
...we made them kneel and bow before us.
And no one stopped us from our conquest.
We got rid of the soldiers in Mekece castle.
And we stopped their evil alliance!
If Allah permits, Mekece will be our
vanguard for the upcoming conquests.
If Allah permits.
Come on now,
share the loot among alps and people.
Long live Osman Bey!
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Long live to you as well.
And the prisoners...
...will wait to hear their verdict.
They will wait.
What's this disgrace!? Who do you
think you are to imprison my Bey!?
We are the owners
of the lands you step on, Melike Hatun!
Know your place.
Osman brought Lords and Beys along with him.
He has the control.
We have to run. We must escape. Come on.
We'll escape. We'll escape.
Before vultures eat my soldiers flesh away...
...we'll destroy this tribe.
Beys are here.
Now you'll talk.
Alps. That's enough rest. Untie them.
We're good.
Don't bother.
The sun warms my bones.
Yes.
It's outdoors.
The tent will suffocate me.
It's outdoors?
The tent will suffocate you?
Konur.
We'll see...
...if you can be this happy...
...when your skin is pulled away.
Alps. Untie them.
Walk.
Congratulations my Bey.
Your decision will herald..
..even bigger wars.
I could kill them all.
But our Ghaza goal won't
lose a single drop of blood.
But...
...Ulcay keeps interrupting us.
Now...
..if we don't reveal he's a traitor...
...we'll be guilty.
Did Boran and Konur make him talk?
Rukneddin The Judge's burial site...
We thought only the murderer,
Orhan and Elcim knew about it.
But Ulcay knows it.
He killed Rukneddin The Judge my Bey.
We know it.
Then he killed Ahmet too.
We must reveal it.
The dog won't talk even if we torture him.
We'll let them get away.
Well...
That's why
I made Boran and Konur go with him.
They can earn his trust.
We'll go after him when the time comes.
We'll only know the truth when the dog is free.
Then we'll release the dog.
Exactly.
We will.
What did
they give you to betray Osman Bey?
Release me and I'll tell you.
You said...
...you'd always side with us Boran Bey.
What happened?
I helped them wake up.
They saw who Osman Bey really is.
You...
You dog, Ulcay.
You helped them wake up?
Now I'll gauge out your eyes.
We'll see if you can still talk.
Baysungur.
A dog will only shut up with a good beating.
We have to kill Osman now.
If not he'll kill us if he finds us.
We're going to kill him...
Once we're out of here...
...I'm going to
burn him to death alongside his tribe.
With so many lies...
...you tried to truck us.
But...
...just as you always do against the truth...
...you lost once again.
Infidel.
To find a way to defeat us...
...they always make a move.
What about you?
The beys of Turks.
How did you become a part of this?
What did you gain?
Tell me, what?
You lost your land.
You have a stain in your past now.
You can't keep us here.
Byzantine will make you
pay for it Osman Bey.
Ask your own beys whatever you want.
But we Byzantine...
We of course have conditions..
...to forsake your life.
Tell the Emperor.
You're going to let go of the Turks
you're holding captive in Byzantine lands.
Those who you arrested for nothing...
...those you're keeping for a ransom. All of them.
Only then...
...will you make it out of here alive.
If riot...
...only your dead bodies will leave these lands.
Don't forget these.
Wait here.
Come on, this way.
Let's leave before the alps wake up.
Where is the stable?
It's not possible to go there.
It's too close to the middle.
Am I to be scared of a handful of alps?
I'll open up my path with blood.
Ulcay.
Put your sword away.
We'll leave without making a noise.
Come on.
Against my beys...
...I have a code that holds me back.
But...
...my religion tells me to be...
...strict towards your kind.
I'm declaring war on Byzantine now.
We won't stop until...
...your land is our land.
Take them away now.
Come on, Beys.
By working with the infidels...
...you made a mistake.
When we wanted to ride our
horses in those lands for ghaza...
...you stopped us from ghaza.
From now on, no one will hide behind trade.
We will not allow speaking of
prosperity, and poisoning the Beys!
And no Turk tribe will..
...trade in Byzantine lands!
What are you talking about Osman Bey?
How dare you to interfere in our trade?
We exposed you.
But I haven't told you
about your verdict yet.
You should pray, so that I won't hang you.
Ulcay got the bait.
He did!
Konur Bey hit me really hard to make him believe.
It would be tough for me if he hadn't believed.
Well, you deserved it
after saying all those words.
Well, Boran Bey acted mercifully.
So, what will happen now?
Konur and Boran will bring the truth to Osman Bey.
As long as there are Beys like you...
...we don't need any enemies!
Your pride and ambition did this to you
For what? Just for power...
...and might! Tell me, what did it get you?
What do you have now? Beys!
I will tell you.
In these lands...
...you have no authority!
In these frontiers, from now on,
only we will be the ones to do trade.
Everything will be under our control.
Bursa, Iznik, Constantinople...
...from East to West, and West to East...
...I stopped all the trade!
No one...
...will trade.
You are killing our livelihood, Osman Bey!
How are you going to stop our trade?
Yakup Bey, you seem to not understand.
Every caravan that comes out of your lands...
...will be attacked.
Then, you are...
...waging
war upon us, together with Byzantine.
All the things you said are
reasons for war, Osman Bey!
Wait, Yakup Bey.
I am not finished yet.
There are things you haven't heard.
Well...
You're so proud of...
...the frontier market.
From now on..
...it is Kayi property.
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
The Frontier Market
is Kayi property from now on.
Come on. Don't wait!
Hang Kayi's sacred flag.
Do it!
Allah is the Greatest!
This flag will shine like a star...
...between all the Turkmens...
...and welcome everyone, I hope.
I hope so, Aykurt.
I hope so.
What are you talking about, Osman Bey?
I have never heard such a thing.
As long as you act scared...
...you'll see many things you've never seen.
Osman Bey...
You know that...
...what you did will have repercussions.
You should be happy...
...that in return for what you did...
...I only take your castle and market.
Come on.
Take the Beys to their tent.
Until I release my judgment...
...they'll be treated as captives.
Go on.
Turk's great Beys...
Look what you did.
My Bey. Someone came a long way to see you.
Peace be with you Osman Bey.
The far away Turk lands send you regards.
Peace be upon you.
We send our regards too.
You came from a long way.
Tell me. What do you wish to say?
We heard you aim for Ghaza.
We wish to fight with you.
Everyone wants to do the same.
You will side with me in war.
Show us the way and we'll fight in front of you.
When the time comes, we'll
die for Ghaza, Osman Bey.
Praise be.
People come and people go.
Thank you.
Welcome to our land.
Thank you my Bey.
Come on.
Today we'll have victory.
Who are you?
Stand back.
I'm here to
take you to Constantine Paleologos.
Greetings to my friend.
Put down your swords.
Who's Constantine?
What does he want?
Let's go. No time.
I'll be back for Osman.
Go to the Green Valley.
I'll find you there.
Then, I'll tell you everything.
They're running away just like that.
Who are they Konur?
Where are they going?
Brother, we have to follow them.
They will do something, it's clear as day.
How can we keep up with them with running, Boran?
Besides, if we go they will know.
That jackal will come back to his inn.
Everything will be revealed soon.
His days are numbered now.
Alps.
Prepare the horses, come on.
We have lots to do.
Gunduz Bey.
Do you have time?
You heard Osman Bey.
We have to stop the
Byzantine help Bursa is getting.
I'm going to Sakarya to build some tribes.
If what you're going
to say isn't something very important...
...then let's speak later.
Gunduz Bey.
The thing that happened the other day.
Those weren't pleasant.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to shout at you.
I respect both your age and experience.
Besides...
..we shouldn't be on bad terms.
We have so much to worry about...
...so we should hold
each other close right Gunduz Bey?
I've fought with the...
...Mongols a for years.
I've seen a lot of bloodshed and death.
So a bey who is old enough to be my son...
...shouting at me did bother me.
But...
...you did what
is suitable for you.
And you destroyed that feeling.
I'm sorry too.
I shouldn't have messed with your knowledge.
Not at all, Gunduz Bey.
Let me tell you this.
Let's
forget what happened Gunduz Bey.
We're all going to be wrapped
in that white cloth one day.
I give you my blessings.
Please give me yours too.
Of course Gunduz Bey, thank you.
But why do you say that?
We're going to fight along
side each other a lot more.
Don't say that.
A big war is on the horizon.
Gaza asks the soldiers to bleed.
In this world where we
can't even control a breath...
...we might live today and be gone tomorrow.
How can one know when
they will give their last breath?
Of course we can't.
That's why until the day we
die we have to live freely...
...and try to be happy right?
Alright, Orhan Bey.
Duty calls.
I trust you with each other..
...and I trust you with my daughter Elcim.
Hold each other tight like the nail and the flesh.
Don't forget.
Elcim has no one but you.
Don't worry Gunduz Bey.
I'll give my life away instead of...
...letting Elcim get hurt.
Come on.
May Allah protect you.
Thank you Gunduz Bey.
With peace, Gunduz Bey.
With peace.
Come on.
Let's hit the road.
We have a long road ahead of us.
My brave brother. Come on.
Alright, brother.
Holofira, the important matter
you wanted to talk about.
What's it?
My duty is over, so
I want to leave the tribe, Osman Bey.
You are like our daughter, Holofira.
Even without a duty, you are always welcomed here.
And, where will you go?
Is this about...
...Orhan and Elcim?
As long as I am here, there will always
be a dark cloud over their marriage.
I don't want to harm their marriage.
Since the beginning, the best
option for all of us was for me to leave.
Do you want to go to Constantinople?
No.
If you allow it,
I want to stay in a monastery in Bursa...
...until you conquer it.
That's the heart of Byzantine.
Even if I leave the tribe, I
want to continue helping you.
They know that you have
been on our side for a while.
They will hold a grudge against you.
This will be a tough duty.
My own aunt sent me to my death.
So it's not hard for me to fight against them.
I will convince them that you tricked
me and wanted to use me as a slave.
Holofira, I know you are a brave girl.
But...
...I can't put you in a danger like this.
After all you did for me, I
owe it to Kayis, Osman Bey.
When you conquer Bursa one day...
...I will be happy to know that I did my part.
Please allow me to do that.
You are showing great courage for us.
So we can't stand in your way.
Okay, my girl.
May Allah enlighten your path.
Thank you.
Ambush! To arms!
Who are you?
Whose tail did I step on this
time to be ambushed like this?
What do you want? Who are you?
Don't worry, you will get to know me!
Take him!
Did you think clearly Holofira?
I did Gonca.
I made up my mind.
I'll live in the Monastery.
What will you do there all alone?
Can't you stay here?
All good things come to
an end eventually, Fatma.
The times we spent together...
...were valuable.
You're leaving.
I am.
It's time to say goodbye.
Goodbye...
...Orhan Bey.
Go safely.
Lord's daughter.
I heard of your victory.
Congratulations my Bey.
EyvAllah.
Welcome my girl.
Alps are ready Bala Hatun.
Good.
What is it? Who's leaving?
I am.
You said you'd stay.
There are no trades with the lords.
My duty is done.
It's time to leave.
Take care of yourselves.
Go safely Holofira.
Thank you.
Come on Elcim.
You were always like a mother to me Bala Hatun.
I find it hard..
...to be away from you.
Mother can't be replaced.
Holofira. I know that.
A mother and a daughter always feels pain.
But it gets better.
You are like a daughter to me.
My prayers will be with you.
Go safely.
Thank you Mother Bala.
Go safely lord's daughter.
May you go with speed...
...and may angels protect you, I hope.
You won't be here at the tribe for long.
You will return...
..in peace.
Will you rage a war against us...
...claiming it's your right?
Frontier Market...
...was Yakup Bey's.
You took it.
Mekece Castle was mine...
...and you took it from me.
When you do things like this...
...how can there be peace?
I won't let you have the frontier market.
There is no more trade.
It's over.
You're going to go.
Either on your foot...
...or being carried in a carriage.
You're going to pay
for what you've done, Osman Bey.
I did everything I did for the unity of the Turks.
But...
...if you're going to stand against me...
...if you're going to stop me...
...then....
...I won't forgive you again.
Can I come in my bey?
Come in.
My bey an alp is here, he's injured.
My bey.
They took Gunduz Bey.
Who?
Byzantine.
But they were different, my bey.
Look at me.
If you're involved in this...
...you won't get to get out of here.
Orhan, Alaeddin.
Come with me.
Orhan.
My dad's alp is injured.
Is there bad news?
Gunduz Bey was ambushed Elcim.
What?
Hold on.
Is he okay? Tell me the truth please.
Come on alps.
-I'll come too.
-Elcim.
We don't have time. We're going
to bring your dad to you, I promise.
Girl come.
Orhan is right. Come on.
We'll take care of her, come on.
Whoever it is that has done this...
...whoever it is that's behind this...
This will be their last day alive.
Come on.
If Gunduz dies...
...Osman will kill us all.
He can't blame us for this too.
I didn't do anything.
That's it.
Just like this you're going to die one by one.
Everyday one of your
corpses will leave this tribe.
Calm down.
He's okay.
The only thing you can get from me is...
..blood and flesh.
Even the ladies in our tribe...
...hit harder than you.
You don't know how to treat the captives Theodore.
Look at Gunduz Bey.
He's covered in blood.
And there
is so many other ways to do this too.
Isn't that so Gunduz Bey?
Ulcay.
Jackal.
My only wish from Allah...
Gunduz can't wish anymore.
Gunduz...
...has turned into a night now.
You ran out of time now, Gunduz Bey.
What are you waiting for then?
Where we are going is clear.
I will never give you what you want.
You can think that. Things changed.
Great emperor sent Konstantin
Paleologos as the protector of Rome.
Your death..
...will be a gift
of protection for Bursa.
Battles require blood as payment.
I am ready to pay for it.
I swear that you won't die easily, Gunduz!
What's on your mind, Ulcay?
Osman must be after me.
He will find my trace eventually.
We will give him a gift first.
While he is wasting his time with
the gift, we will go to Paleologos.
Get out of the way, Gonca.
Stop.
So you hate me to the degree to
have me killed, huh Yakup Bey?
What does that mean?
I am talking about the Byzantine
soldiers you sent after the caravan.
Did you not send them?
Gonca.
You...
Were you in that caravan?
Did you not know?
Since you want to kill me...
...I am right in front of you.
Yakup Bey, you don't have
to send infidels behind me!
When you slapped me, you set my heart on fire!
You killed my love for you already.
But it wasn't enough, huh?
Okay.
I am here.
Come on.
Draw your sword and kill me, Yakup Bey!
My father wouldn't do that,
Gonca! Come to your senses!
Am I lying?
Did you not send them?
We did.
We established that
caravan together with Holofira.
Everyone
knew that I would be in that caravan.
But you did not?
But...
..but I did not know.
I did not know.
I wish...
...I wish I could believe you.
I would really want that.
What are you talking about, dad?
Melike Hatun said it.
I guess...
...all along...
...she wanted Gonca to die.
They were going to have me kill my girl.
My Bey. They're Gunduz Bey's alps.
Yes.
My Bey. Boran Bey's coming.
My Bey.
We were moving with Ulcay.
Byzantines showed up.
They weren't regular soldiers.
Ulcay went with them.
He sent us to send word to
Germiyanids and Candarbeys.
Bastard. Where did he go Konur?
We'd follow him but...
...we couldn't make it.
Ulcay told us to go to Green Valley.
Okay.
They're after Gunduz Bey. They'll kill him.
We can come my Bey.
No.
We must kill Ulcay today.
You will go there as he said.
We'll go after Gunduz Bey.
As you wish my Bey.
Give horses to Boran and Konur.
Bury the martyrs.
As you wish my Bey.
Yes my Bey.
Come.
You have no mercy.
You tied him up.
He could be free one last time.
Allah will punish you.
You demons.
Your evil..
...won't make me obey you.
Never.
I like to bury men alive Theodoros.
But it's different now.
We'll play a game with Gunduz Bey.
Right Gunduz Bey?
You can't die just yet.
Get him up.
This will stop Osman...
...and anger him Ulcay.
I wish...
...I could stay and see Osman's face.
My Bey!
There are traces.
They're new and alike.
These tracks lead to north.
They do it on purpose my Bey.
They want to lead us where they want.
All we can do is find Gunduz Bey.
Osman Bey!
Osman Bey.
Gunduz Bey.
I'm here.
Osman Bey.
Bring the rope. Come on.
Gunduz Bey, hold on.
Come on alps, kids come on.
Come on.
Hold the rope Gunduz Bey.
Hold it.
Come on.
We're going to fight so many on top
of our horses Gunduz Bey, hold on.
Hold on.
Come on.
Oh Allah.
Come on. Allah.
Gunduz Bey.
Are you okay?
Are you?
Osman Bey...
Constantin, Paleologos...
I know.
Ulcay...
I know it all, don't worry.
I know it all.
Alaeddin come on help him.
My bey.
He's not doing okay.
Give me some cloth.
In the name
of Allah, the merciful, the beneficent.
Hold on Gunduz Bey. Hold on.
He will hold on, of course he will.
Right Gunduz Bey?
You are the rock behind our backs.
Of course you will.
Who will we trust then? Who?
No, don't leave us alone.
Come on.
You're never alone Osman Bey.
A whole nation stands with you.
They stand behind you like a rock.
I want you to see it too.
You're going to see it too.
...have to
give back the life that was trusted...
...to me now Osman Bey.
Elcim..
I trust you...
...and ...
...you with her.
My son Orhan.
Don't worry.
Don't worry Gunduz Bey.
I will protect her with my life.
I will protect her with my
life Gunduz Bey, don't worry.
Take Bursa..
...Osman Bey.
Don't worry.
I swear to Allah..
...Bursa...
...will be Turks' land, if Allah permits.
If Allah permits.
I bear witness that there is none
worthy of worship except Allah, and I ...
...bear witness that
Mohammad is His servant and messenger.
From Allah we came, to Him is our return.
First, Gunduz Bey...
...then...
...everyone
from your household..
Ulcay...
Gunduz then everyone huh?
I'm going to find you.
This...
...will be your last day.
You won't live another day.
I'm going to show you what it means to...
...touch one of us.
Gunduz Bey's kidnapping is not good.
If anything happens to him...
Osman will leave none of us alive.
Are we going to stay for death here?
Do something.
Ibrahim Bey!
Watch it, Yakup Bey!
I will ask you only one question.
When we
sent soldiers to stop Kayi's caravan...
...did you know that Gonca was there?
What are you implying, Yakup Bey?
Did you send your soldiers
knowing that Gonca was there!?
I did not know.
Melike Hatun.
Did you know?
You almost made me kill my daughter!
I did not know either, but...
...did you not disown her?
Does it matter her being in that caravan?
You knew!
You knew it, Melike
Hatun! You sent my sister to her death
I did not know, don't you hear me?
But weren't you going to kill that
girl who brought you disgrace?
She is valuable now?
She is my daughter! She is my blood!
I am her father!
Even with her...
...mistakes and wrong doings, she is my daughter!
Yakup Bey!
Control yourself...
...and your voice!
I understand it now Ibrahim Bey.
This is where we part ways
Orhan.
Father!
Who did it Osman Bey?
Constantine Paleologos.
He...
...is working with Ulcay.
We'll see him when we kill him.
Elcim.
We'll make them pay.
I promise you.
Bala.
You should..
...stay with Elcim. She's in pain.
Support her.
Don't worry.
Father!
My condolences Osman Bey.
Gunduz..
...was a brave Bey.
My condolences.
The man behind this...
...was your soldier Ulcay.
Ibrahim Bey.
Why would Ulcay kill Gunduz Bey?
The same reason why he killed our men...
...all this time.
What are you saying Osman Bey?
I said it before.
I'll say it again.
If you were....
..involved in this...
...and if I prove it...
...then I'll bury you in dirt.
First I'll prove Ulcay did it.
Then it's your turn.
I won't cry until my father's killers...
...are caught and punished.
We won't cry now.
I promise my Hatun.
Those traitors will pay for it.
Swords will talk now.
Attention!
Osman Bey!
Girl.
Are you feeling better?
I am.
Hold on girl.
I hope Allah grants you patience.
Thank you Bala Hatun.
Osman Bey.
Those who did this to my dad...
Don't worry.
They're going to pay for it.
Ulcay and those Byzantine dogs who support him.
We're going to end them all.
When will we have the funeral my bey?
Before Gunduz Bey's blood is dried...
...that Ulcay will go into his grave.
And we will fulfill our duty.
Allow me...
...to come.
No.
You will fulfill your last duty as well girl.
Don't worry, we got it from here.
We're going to take Gunduz Bey's revenge, Elcim.
Don't worry.
Osman ridiculed Candar and
Germiyan in front of the folk.
Like that wasn't enough
he's keeping us in his tribe.
Osman keeps his enemies
right in front of him Mehmet.
What else does he have to
do that he keeps us here dad?
He made us take the blame for his faults too.
How will we get rid of this?
When...
...Osman reveals his intent...
..we will make our move.
But...
...our unity with Ibrahim Bey...
...has damaged us greatly.
Their blind rage worked
in Osman's favor.
There is no partnership no more.
We're going to retake the leadership.
Can I come in my bey?
Come in.
My bey, the Kayi alps want to enter the tent.
Osman.
Osman isn't sitting still dad.
How can I?
Let them in.
Let's see what they have to say.
As you wish my dad.
Entering like...
...you're attacking
at this hour, what does this mean Cerkutay?
With Osman Bey's order...
...we're going to take Mehmet Bey capture.
Has Osman lost his mind?
How dare he?
Even patience has it's limits.
Osman Bey's decision is final.
To stop a war between the two beyhoods...
...for a while...
...Mehmet Bey will be our captive.
Dad...
...allow me to take his head off.
Mehmet.
Osman turned his back to you.
I took care of you.
Your son.
Your family.
You.
I gave you a tent where you could live.
You've shared your meals with Mehmet.
And now are you going to take him?
I will.
Osman Bey...
..never turned his back to me.
His path was mine as well.
My loyalty...
...was always to him.
Treacherous dog
Mehmet's life is my care.
If you don't make a mistake...
...he won't be hurt, Yakup Bey.
Excuse us.
A fire fell onto Kayi tribe.
Don't let it grow bigger.
Mehmet, let go.
Dad!
Let go!
If anything happens to Mehmet...
...you will pay for it, Cerkutay!
Beware!
Alps.
Take Mehmet Bey.
Let go!
Cerkutay, Osman will not get away with this!
Speak Osman Bey.
Did you call us here to humiliate us?
Mehmet Bey, let's listen to him first.
Mehmet.
Don't follow your father.
When you stand behind me...
...your fathers will stop.
You are not keeping us as
prisoners just for this, right?
You must have another goal.
I will show you the truth.
What truth.
The truth that the enemies try to cover up.
Don't you see us as your enemies, Osman Bey?
If I saw you as enemies...
...you wouldn't be here.
Come on, get ready. We will depart at dawn.
We are almost there.
I will continue alone.
We should come with you for a little longer.
Bursa soldiers shouldn't see you.
Let's say our goodbyes here.
Okay.
Ulgen hatun.
You always treat me like a big sister.
Well, I did not do much.
You were never happy ever
since you came to the tribe.
I hope you will find peace in Bursa.
I am glad for everything I
experienced together with Kayis.
I wish my departure will be
the happy days for everyone.
Ameen, if Allah permits.
Come on!
Allah Allah!
Tugay is nowhere to be found, Hatun.
My Bey.
Andra's gone too.
Ibrahim Bey.
They'll kill us all.
And we're just waiting.
May I come in Ibrahim Bey.
Come.
Bala Hatun expects you.
Is that right?
She's calling us?
If Bala Hatun wants to speak...
...she can come here.
I won't go to anyone.
Bala Hatun ordered me.
You will go Ibrahim Bey.
We could take you by force.
But we'll do it. Just so you know.
You really make us...
...feel like captives.
We'll have to go.
Where were you Ulcay?
I haven't been this happy in a long time.
What is it?
Kayi's great bey...
...Gunduz.
The land he called his own..
..is now his grave.
He died.
Congratulations.
What about Osman?
Won't he follow us?
Of course.
But Osman..
...is an injured wolf.
We're not alone anymore.
Constantine Paleologos.
He's with us now.
Soon he'll be here.
I sent word.
Who is Constantine?
A man feared by even the
greatest Byzantine commanders.
He massacred the lands
between Balkans and the east.
He's only loyal to the Emperor.
He'll be here now.
Well...
Osman wants war.
And we'll do our part.
We'll bring war to these lands.
But first...
...I'll kill Osman's family one by one.
How will we do it?
You'll see.
Constantine Paleologos.
Now we know who to attack.
That bastard.
He was a snake.
Ibrahim Bey will kill him.
Hold on.
You didn't hear everything yet.
These are only words.
Now it's time for arrogance.
You'll hear everything.
Everything.
Bala Hatun.
You made us come here. What's so urgent?
Have a seat Ibrahim Bey.
Here.
You made us come here.
And now you order us.
We have no time to sit.
What will you speak about?
All you do is talk since we got here.
-But it's all nonsense!
-Either you don't hear me...
...or you don't understand,
Melike Hatun.
Bala Hatun.
Tell me what's important.
Gonca, it looks a bit dark in here right?
Can you go and light those up?
Let us see each other more clearly.
Okay mother.
I'm running out of patience Bala Hatun.
Come to the conclusion.
Osman Bey.
He went to get
Ulcay, Ibrahim Bey.
About that fake judge thing.
Bala Hatun.
I've told Osman Bey this too.
We have nothing to do with this fake judge.
Why are you still asking this?
Then you must not know that the fake
judge was from your lands, Ibrahim Bey.
And he was punished because
he was unfair in his cases.
What
are you two trying to say right now?
What are you saying?
Ibrahim Bey, let's go.
Hold on Melike Hatun.
We're talking here.
Why are you scared of?
Your lies...
..or your sins?
Didn't you kill
Rukneddin The Judge to get my son killed?
Hold on there.
What are you saying Bala Hatun?
Melike.
Think about it Ibrahim Bey.
Think.
The court ending quickly.
Alaeddin being punished by death.
Who else would want that apart from you?
Even if it's not you...
...then his mother.
She's lying.
You took my son's life first...
...and now you're trying to get in between us.
I won't stay here longer.
Ibrahim Bey let's go.
That's not it either, Melike Hatun.
I've heard it.
You've looked into the witches near here.
How can you try to do something
that Allah has made a sin?
Melike.
Your lies never end.
I won't stay here anymore. Move.
Fearing for your life Melike Hatun?
Don't be scared.
You won't die.
Let go.
Not just Rukneddin The Judge, Ibrahim Bey.
Your wife placed a poisoned candle in our room...
...and tried to kill us too.
We heard it from the witch she went to.
Don't be scared.
She got her punishment as well.
Osman.
Did you think that the wolf
wouldn't smell the scent of the jackal?
If you tried to trick one of us...
But that's how things work.
Jackal set up a trap...
...and you fall for it.
Look? That's the case again.
Just in time beys.
First Gunduz...
...then you.
You can't run Osman.
We won't escape, huh?
Who says we are afraid of death?
We live with death!
Did Gunduz Bey beg you?
Either by begging, or bravely.
You can't change the truth.
This time, you can't do anything.
I set up the trap for you Osman.
I knew you would follow
me. I took all the precautions.
All the precautions.
First, you lost to your ambition...
...and now you will lose to me!
I killed Ahmet.
I raided Karacahisar market.
I killed the judge with my own hands!
Now I will kill you.
Even the sheytaan couldn't
think of the things this bastard did!
Let's go and kill him
Stop, Mehmet Bey.
Let him finish.
Control yourself, Mehmet.
It looks like we have more to hear.
How could you do this, Hatun?
Did you really kill dear judge?
How could I know, my Bey?
How could I know that
the murderer of our son is a Byzantian...
Shut up!
You brought me disgrace! Shut up.
I don't want to hear you.
Our son's killer is found!
No.
Ibrahim Bey, he wasn't the killer.
What are you saying, Bala Hatun?
He was!
That Byzantine man
The scheme is greater than that.
The killer of your son that dog called Ulcay.
Someone else was holding
his leash. It was all his plan.
He wants
to make Turkmens fight each other.
Osman Bey is after him now.
He will catch that trickster.
Ulcay.
Do you know what I am going
to do after I kill you and your son?
I will...
...place Germiyan and Candar flags here!
You act with Olcaytu's orders
and try to devise a scheme, huh?
The Turks who hear
this won't be able to get united again.
Osman.
Your dreams will not com true.
If you acted on your own...
...you would
realize that this is not just my cause.
But you couldn't comprehend that.
Now, if my flag falls...,
...you will see that others will pick it up.
Olcaytu will see it too!
I will kill whoever picks it up, too!
The land and the sky belongs to us!
As long as Ilkhanid Empire
lives, only their flag flies!
I will crush you now.
But...
...I will do it alone.
Come here.
I came here for two things.
First, what you'll confess.
And your worthless body.
Attack!
We're here my Bey.
Allah is the Greatest!
Konur!
Konur let's go!
My Bey.
Ibrahim Bey.
Ibrahim.
Don't believe them.
Shut up
What have you done?
What have you done Hatun?
Did you do sorcery?
Did you kill the Great Turk...
...Rukneddin The Judge?
I did it out of pain my Bey.
I did it...
...because I was in pain.
Shut up!
You are full of sin.
I won't let you get away with it.
You'll pay for it.
But...
...until we go back home...
...you won't make another mistake.
Ibrahim Bey.
Bala.
I won't let you get away with it.
This is the lands boys become men
We'll before dogs take over!
Oh Allah!
Gunduz Bey has just died.
And I'll kill
you for it Theodore.
Come here.
Soldiers! Soldiers!
What is it?
Are you actually not that brave?
Revenge is swiftly held with us Theodore.
Now...
...Gunduz Bey will rest in peace.
You killing me will change nothing.
Constantine is coming for you.
Let him, it doesn't matter.
The only place he will go....
...is hell.
Konur, you traitor.
I should've known.
What were you when you
infiltrating Ibrahim Bey's people?
You lowlife dog.
Did you think we wouldn't know that you would run?
I was never loyal to you Ulcay.
You were my hardest duty, Ulcay.
Get up.
Move.
Move!
Here...
...is the one has concealed
the truth and changed it.
Now...
...we're going to take him to the tribe.
So that...
...the beys can see him too.
We saw the reason and the result
of your patience, Osman Bey. Thank you.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Think of me as a father now.
We didn't think
of you as other but as one of our own.
Move now.
Move.
Osman Bey was right.
It was clear that he was but we
resisted not to see it Mehmet Bey.
That Ulcay...
He fooled us all this time.
Lowlife scum.
Friend of Kayis who
enslaved me and released me
in exchange of slave Turks
thus embarrassing me...
...Princess Holofira.
How dare you come-here?
Commander Alexius.
Please allow me to explain.
Explain
Are you going to explain how you
worked with our arch nemesis Turks?
Explain it.
Never.
I would never work with them Commander.
I am just a sinner who
has faced the Turks' wrath.
Orhan.
He made me believe his love...
...and then married a Turk.
Not a friend..
...but I'm their biggest enemy.
Do you think that we won't make you pay for
the foolishness of believing in a Turk's love?
Why are you,here?
Please don't throw my sin in my face, Commander.
Allow me to beg for
forgiveness from Jesus Christ...
...and be of your service till I die.
Allow me to stay at the Monastery.
A sinner like you in a Monastery?
I would've killed you a long
time ago if it was up to me.
But Constantine will make the decision about you.
Until Commander Constantine is here,
she will stay in the dungeons. Take her.
Move.
-Killer.
-Move.
-You killer.
-Traitor.
-Kill him.
-Killer.
Move!
Gunduz Bey has become a
martyr and reached the afterlife...
...but you will go to hell, you bastard!
Stop.
Solgur Aga.
Traitor!
Move!
Elcim.
My father will do what's necessary.
It was all because of you.
Dervish.
It's the great
Allah who starts and finishes everything.
We will return to him eventually.
We-will return to him'eventually.
What really matters is how
we are going to return to him.
With dignity, or a black heart?
Either hell or heaven.
This tribe will become your hell.
People should know what lies behind
their words, and shouldn't speak ill words.
In this hell of a world, words can kill.
Move now!
Move!
Come here!
This jackal...
...everyone
thought of him as Ibrahim Bey's man!
But in truth, he served fitna, cruelty...
...and Olcaytu
He worked with Byzantine!
Whoever stood against us...
...he worked with them!
Our kin did not do something different either.
This dog killed Rukneddin The Judge!
And...
...he killed Ahmet Bey!
Is that right?
Is that right, Ulcay!?
Ask your sons.
Tell your Beys about it.
Is that right, Mehmet?
That's right, father.
He confessed it himself.
He took part in Gunduz Bey's death too.
I fed you for years! And you killed Ahmed
What did you want from Ahmed
You bastard!
Why didn't you kill me!?
Stop there, Ibrahim Bey.
Your scale of justice was never right.
You never accepted the truth.
That's why, you can't bring the justice!
Beys, calm down.
We spent lots of time together, right?
Well, first of all...
...you raided Karacahisar market, right?
Tell them about it.
Ulcay's not the only sinner.
Not true.
Shut up!
Osman Bey!
Before he dies..
..he wants to cause chaos.
We have nothing to do with a market raid.
Ulcay Wants to slander our name.
...were born men...
...but we die a jackal.
You will always...
..be snakes.
And you...
...worked with Ulcay.
Olcaytu's orders...
...led you to sin against us.
You wanted us to kill each other.
We always stopped that.
Why?
So we won't kill our brothers.
This dog will die here.
And you'll get the hell out of my lands.
Osman Bey.
You won't even let me kill my son's killer.
You're the ones who brought
these bastards to our land.
Despite that, we don't make you pay for it.
Know that...
..it's out of mercy.
It's because...
...we don't kill our brothers.
Osman Bey.
As long as you have snakes around you...
...you don't need another enemy.
Shut up!
If dogs like you never came to our land...
...no one would deceit our men.
From now on..
...we won't work to convince traitors.
Nicea and Bursa will be under siege.
The oppressor's land will be ours.
And this dog...
...will be eaten by birds.
Yunus Emre..-.
...said it perfectly.
An eye for an eye.
This dog will die...
...will die like Ahmet Bey.
Our only rule...
...is to have no mercy...
..for the oppressor.
This dog died.
And you will get the hell out of my land.
If you ever show your faces...
...then...
...I will come
for you with my sword.
Oh Allah.
Help me to stand against the oppressors.
Give me the strength to fight for the weak.
Ameen.
You did good.
We fulfilled our last duty my bey.
My bey.
Was it our last one?
Will you be able to forgive us?
People make mistakes.
You...
...payed for the price of your mistakes.
But while you were paying for it...
...you didn't stop helping our nation.
Thank you.
That's why...
...you deserve to be forgiven.
Thank you my bey.
May Allah give you a long life.
What's important is...
What's important is the nation.
What's important is our rules.
Now.
We get our strength from you.
We trust you fully.
If you make a mistake...
...then the
nation makes a mistake.
This will be never...
...repeated.
Never, my bey.
Cerkutay.
My bey.
Give them their belongings.
As you wish my bey.
I've taken care of these swords like my own.
Finally they're reunited with their owners.
Thanks brother.
Gunduz Bey who we got strength from until now...
Now we're going to fulfill our last duty for him.
Dad...
My dad whose heart was set
ablaze with the love for ghaza.
We took the life of the one who did this to you.
We're going to find who is behind this too.
I promise, dad.
Now you're a martyr.
And I'm an orphan.
But don't worry dad.
Your tribe..
...and your people will be under my care.
Even if I'm left all alone...
...I will protect them with my life dad.
I swear.
What are you saying Elcim?
You're not alone.
Not at all.
We're a family now.
From now on..
...I'll always be with you.
Don't look at me like that.
I know what those eyes are telling me.
But I promise you.
I promise...
...I'll always be there for you.
Gunduz Bey...
...trusted me with you.
I'll never leave you alone.
My dad is coming here to bury Gunduz Bey.
We should cover him.
In the name
of Allah, the merciful, the beneficent.
Go ahead.
Yakup Bey.
Before I leave, I will tell you...
...about the truth.
I did not know you were in the caravan.
Believe it if you want.
Or don't.
I believe it.
Are you...
...going there to-
No.
I stand behind what I said.
I told you the truth...
I told you the truth..
...so that you
wouldn't confuse me with yourselves.
Come on Mehmet.
One day, you will regret choosing
this life, and ignoring your family.
Mehmet, she is deaf to the truth.
It's futile talking to her.
Come on.
Enough!
Enough Yakup Bey!
You are the one who is deaf to the truth!
You are the one who can't see the truth!
I will not allow you to make my
hatun sad with your stone hearts!
Shut up Alaeddin
Or I am going to kill you
You ruined our family!
If you loved Gonca..
...you wouldn't punish her with this loneliness.
Mehmet.
Gonca is not alone, Mehmet Bey!
Gonca has her husband behind her.
And behind him, we stand.
Kayi tribe
You can't scare us with loneliness!
Safe travels to you.
Come on Mehmet!
...has delivered his soul to Allah today.
We know...
...that death and life...
...are under Allah's command.
May Allah lead us to the way of victory.
We faced many horrid traps.
Our hearts were pierced by evil arrows.
But our fallen soldiers are martyrs...
...and our survivors are ghazi.
Thank Allah.
Hang on Elcim Hatun.
Hang on.
Today, for the Ultimate Order...
...we had another martyr.
But we'll have a thousand more.
The pain we feel for Gunduz Bey...
...won't be seen by the enemy.
Like Gunduz Bey...
...many brave soldiers have passed.
But we will avenge them.
We will!
My son.
Ahmet.
How can I leave my heart here and leave?
How can I leave?
Shut up!
Melike Hatun.
I will punish you...
...when we get to Sinop.
Shut up now.
My son..
I'll go now.
But not because I give up.
I'll come back stronger.
These lands you rest in...
...I won't let Osman have them.
I'll take all of the lands he has.
And...
..I'll be back...
...to punish him and his family.
Come on Melike Hatun.
I won't follow you anymore Ibrahim Bey.
Where are you going Tugay?
You don't follow Allah's path.
I'll go where I belong now.
Come on Hatun.
I swear...
...I won't let Gonca stay there.
I'll kill Alaeddin if I have to.
But I won't let Gonca stay there.
He took my daughter.
He took my market.
He took my daughter's trust in me.
You're going to pay for these Osman.
You're going to pay for these.
What will I tell to Sadet?
How can I..
...leave my daughter here?
Dad.
I'm okay.
I'm leaving my heart here.
But I'll be back.
I'll come back stronger than before.
We will be back Mehmet.
We will be back.
Now...
...we're going
to send Gunduz Bey to his resting place.
Don't forget this.
The blood we shed..
...is never for nothing.
The blood of our martyrs...
...is the messenger of a great nation...
...and the seed of a great nation.
If Allah permits!
Come on.
May Allah forgive his sins.
In the name
of Allah, the merciful, the beneficent.
Oh Allah, in the name of Allah,
the merciful, the beneficent.
Allah is the Greatest!
There is none worthy of worship except Allah.
Conquer Bursa, Osman Bey.
I will conquer Bursa and every other city!
I will bring justice to this corrupt system!
Visit turkision.com for more!